[
    {
        "question": "祝日",
        "optionA": "しゅくか",
        "optionB": "しゅくにち",
        "optionC": "しゅくひ",
        "optionD": "しゅくじつ",
        "answer": "しゅくじつ"
    },

    {
        "question": "工場",
        "optionA": "こじょう",
        "optionB": "こうじょ",
        "optionC": "こうじょう",
        "optionD": "こじょ",
        "answer": "こうじょう"
    },

    {
        "question": "道路",
        "optionA": "どろ",
        "optionB": "みちろ",
        "optionC": "どうろ",
        "optionD": "みちろう",
        "answer": "どうろ"
    },

    {
        "question": "村",
        "optionA": "まち",
        "optionB": "えき",
        "optionC": "むら",
        "optionD": "うち",
        "answer": "むら"
    },

    {
        "question": "弟",
        "optionA": "おとおと",
        "optionB": "おとうと",
        "optionC": "いもおと",
        "optionD": "いもうと",
        "answer": "おとうと"
    },

    {
        "question": "人間",
        "optionA": "じんげん",
        "optionB": "にんかん",
        "optionC": "にんげん",
        "optionD": "じんかん",
        "answer": "にんげん"
    },

    {
        "question": "しめして",
        "optionA": "示して",
        "optionB": "表して",
        "optionC": "占して",
        "optionD": "告して",
        "answer": "示して"
    },

    {
        "question": "綿",
        "optionA": "わた",
        "optionB": "きん",
        "optionC": "きぬ",
        "optionD": "せん",
        "answer": "わた"
    },

    {
        "question": "沸騰",
        "optionA": "ふつしょう",
        "optionB": "ふっとう",
        "optionC": "ぶっどう",
        "optionD": "ぶつしょう",
        "answer": "ふっとう"
    },

    {
        "question": "強盗",
        "optionA": "ごとう",
        "optionB": "きょうどう",
        "optionC": "ごうとう",
        "optionD": "ごうどう",
        "answer": "ごうどう"
    },

    {
        "question": "うやまう",
        "optionA": "尊う",
        "optionB": "礼う",
        "optionC": "敬う",
        "optionD": "貴う",
        "answer": "敬う"
    },

    {
        "question": "しゅっせ",
        "optionA": "昇世",
        "optionB": "出世",
        "optionC": "昇成",
        "optionD": "出成",
        "answer": "出世"
    },

    {
        "question": "台所",
        "optionA": "たいどころ",
        "optionB": "だいところ",
        "optionC": "たいところ",
        "optionD": "だいどころ",
        "answer": "だいどころ"
    },

    {
        "question": "病人",
        "optionA": "びょうしん",
        "optionB": "びょうにん",
        "optionC": "びょうじん",
        "optionD": "びょういん",
        "answer": "びょうにん"
    },

    {
        "question": "停止",
        "optionA": "ていし",
        "optionB": "ていじ",
        "optionC": "てし",
        "optionD": "てしい",
        "answer": "ていし"
    }
]